<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Registration_page</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="server_problem">Response</string>
    <string name="Rs">₹</string>
   <string name="Select_the_compaint">Select_the_compaint</string>
    <string name="Privacy_Policy"><b><font color="#000000">(a)</font></b> Soliteck recognizes the expectations of its customers with regard to privacy, confidentiality and security of their personal information that resides with Soliteck.\n
    <b><font color="#000000">(b)</font></b> This Privacy Policy provides you with details about the manner in which your data is collected, stored &amp; used by us. You are advised to read this Privacy Policy carefully.\n
    <b><font color="#000000">(c)</font></b> By visiting Soliteck website/WAP site/applications you expressly give us consent to use &amp; disclose your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of the policy, please do not use or access Soliteck website, WAP site or mobile applications.\n
    <b><font color="#000000">(d)</font></b> Note: Our privacy policy may change at any time without prior notification. To make sure that you are aware of any changes, kindly review the policy periodically. This Privacy Policy shall apply uniformly to Soliteck desktop website, Soliteck mobile WAP site &amp; Soliteck mobile applications</string>

    <string name="General"> <b><font color="#000000">(a)</font></b> We will not sell, share or rent your personal information to any 3rd party or use your email address/mobile number for unsolicited emails and/or SMS.\n
        <b><font color="#000000">(b) </font></b>Any emails and/or SMS sent by Soliteck will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services &amp; products and this Privacy Policy.\n
        <b><font color="#000000">(c) </font></b>Periodically, we may reveal general statistical information about Soliteck &amp; its users, such as number of visitors, number and type of goods and services purchased, etc.\n
        <b><font color="#000000">(d)</font></b> We reserve the right to communicate your personal information to any third party that makes a legally-compliant request for its disclosure. </string>

    <string name="Personal_Information"> <b><font color="#000000">(a)</font></b> Personal Information means and includes all information that can be linked to a specific individual or to identify any individual, such as name, address, mailing address, telephone number, email ID, credit card number, cardholder name, card expiration date, information about your mobile phone, DTH service, data card, electricity connection, Smart Tags and any details that may have been voluntarily provide by the user in connection with availing any of the services on Soliteck When you browse through Soliteck, we may collect information regarding the domain and host from which you access the internet, the Internet Protocol [IP] address of the computer or Internet service provider [ISP] you are using, and anonymous site statistical data. </string>

    <string name="Cookies"> <b><font color="#000000">(a)</font></b> A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a web server on a web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Soliteck uses cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered.\n
            <b><font color="#000000"> (b)</font></b> No personal information will be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. </string>

    <string name="links_Other_Sites"> <b><font color="#000000">(a)</font></b> Our site links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. Soliteck is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites. </string>


    <string name="Security"> <b><font color="#000000">(a)</font></b> Soliteck has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.\n
        <b><font color="#000000">(b)</font></b> Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.</string>

    <string name="Consent"> <b><font color="#000000">(a)</font></b> By using Soliteck and/or by providing your information, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on Soliteck in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to your consent for sharing your information as per this privacy policy. </string>

    <string name="Communication"> <b><font color="#000000">(a)</font></b> For any kind of communication, please write to support@Soliteck.comSoliteck is headquartered at:Mumbai</string>

    <string name="checkbox"> As the authorized representative,Hereby confirm that I have accepted and agreed to abide by all the terms and conditions outlined in the Privacy Policy. I understand that any failure to comply with the terms or any breach of the agreement may result in legal action being taken against me, effective as of </string>

    //>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>User Agreement>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>

    <string name="agreement1">  THIS AGREEMENT IS AN ELECTRONIC RECORD IN TERMS OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY ACT, 200 AND RULES THERE UNDER AS APPLICABLE AND THE AMENDED PROVISIONS PERTAINING TO ELECTRONIC RECORDS/DOCUMENTS IN VARIOUS STATUTES AS AMENDED BY THE INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY ACT, 2000. THIS IS A COMPUTER GENERATED ELECTRONIC RECORD AND DOES NOT REQUIRE ANY PHYSICAL OR DIGITAL SIGNATURES.   </string>
    <string name="agreement2nd">  PLEASE READ THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT CAREFULLY. TERMS AND CONDITIONS MENTIONED IN THE AGREEMENT ARE A BINDING CONTRACT BETWEEN SOLITECK Private Limited. (COMPANY or SOLITECK),REFERRED HEREIN BELOW AND YOU   </string>
    <string name="agreement3rd"> THE TERMS ARE EFFECTIVE UPON ACCEPTANCE AND WILL GOVERN THE RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN YOU</string>
    <string name="aggrement3rdnew">This Agreement is entered into on this Date</string>
    <string name="aggrement4">  between Soliteck Dgisolutions pvt ltd. a company incorporated under the Companies Act, 1956 and having its Registered Office at Office No. 101 Row house, Plot- 211, Sector-5, Ghansoli, Navi Mumbai Maharashtra - 400 701 (hereinafter referred to as “SoliTeck” , which expression shall, unless it be repugnant to the subject or context thereof, mean and include its successors and assigns) of the ONE PART</string>
    <string name="aggrement5"> a company having its Registered Office at (hereinafter </string>
    <string name="aggrement6">referred to as “the Entity” which</string>
    <string name="aggrement7">expression shall, unless it be</string>
    <string name="aggrement8"> repugnant to the subject or context thereof, mean and include its successors, affiliates and assigns) of the OTHER PART The Entity and SOLITECK are hereinafter collectively referred to as ‘Party’ or ‘Parties’ as per the context.</string>
    <string name="aggrement9"><b><font color="#000000"> WHEREAS </font></b></string>
    <string name="aggrement10"><b><font color="#000000">(i)</font></b> SoliTeck is engaged, inter alia, in the business of enabling electronic payment transactions and payment services and has business arrangements with various mobile operators, payment aggregators, billing companies, Banks and other entities for managing various electronic payments and transaction services;</string>
    <string name="aggrement11"><b><font color="#000000">(ii)</font></b>  The Entity has a pan India network of retail outlets in multiple formats from where customers can access various facilities offered by SOLITECK directly through the Entity;</string>
    <string name="aggrement12"><b><font color="#000000">(iii)</font></b>  The Entity is now proposing to offer Top Up or cell phone refill , DMT services , AEPS services and BBPS services that will enable people to receive the services at the Entity’s Terminals located at the retail outlets as also directly through the Entity and in that context is desirous of tie-ing up with SOLITECK who has in turn tied up with bank &amp; Service Providers.\n <b><font color="#000000">(iv) </font></b>SOLITECK has agreed to the tie up with the Entity, upon the terms and conditions hereinafter appearing.</string>
    <string name="aggrement13"> The parties wish to set up a strategic business alliance and this is likely to involve them disclosing confidential information to each other.\n <b><font color="#000000">1. DEFINITIONS </font></b> \nIn this Agreement the following expressions have the meaning set opposite: \n <b><font color="#000000">this Agreement: </font></b> this document, as amended from time to time in accordance with clause; \n  <b><font color="#000000">A Business Day: </font></b> Monday to Saturday (inclusive) except bank or national holidays in India;\n<b><font color="#000000">Confidential Information: </font></b>each party's confidential information including any Intellectual Property and Know-how disclosed by that party to the other for the Specified Purpose and identified as confidential before or at the time of disclosure;\n <b><font color="#000000">A Group Company: </font></b>any undertaking which is, on or after the date of this Agreement from time to time, a subsidiary undertaking of the Company, a parent undertaking of the Company or a subsidiary undertaking of a parent undertaking of the Company, as those terms are defined in section 258 of the Companies Act 1985; \n <b><font color="#000000">Intellectual Property:</font></b>patents, trade marks, service marks, registered designs, copyrights, database rights, design rights, confidential information, applications for any of the above, and any similar right recognized from time to time in any jurisdiction, together with all rights of action in relation to the infringement of any of the above;\n<b><font color="#000000">THE COMPANY </font></b> SOLITECK is a service provider company engage in the business of Prepaid/Postpaid recharge, DMT service, AEPS, BBPS, and has acquired vast knowledge, experience and expertise therein. And, has a good number of reputed clients and qualified staff with a good location.\nNow it is hereby agreed by and between the parties hereto as follows:</string>
    <string name="aggrement14"><b><font color="#000000">(a)</font></b>SOLITECK appoints the CHANNEL PARTNER for its promotion, marketing and/or selling on a non-exclusive basis for the promotion, marketing, sales and/or Distribution of the said products developed, promoted, marketed, sold, distributed through SMS or Web under its respective brand names.\n<b><font color="#000000">(b)</font></b> Not with standing anything to the contrary herein contained, SOLITECK shall deemed to be entitled from time as it may consider necessary desirable or expedient to promote and market the sale of the said products in the said territory and in particular, to appoint or engage from time to time any other persons, firms, companies or bodies corporate as its CHANNEL PARTNERs and/or representatives in such territory for the promotion, marketing, sale and distribution of the said products in the said territory.">expression shall, unless it be</string>
    <string name="aggrement15">The CHANNEL PARTNER undertakes and agrees that it shall, during the continuance of this Agreement, observe and perform the terms and conditions herein contained and in particular, shall: \n<b><font color="#000000">    (a)</font></b> Is not carrying on any illegal activity;\n <b><font color="#000000">   (b)</font></b> Is not debarred from entering into above contract with SOLITECK under any law or rule;\n<b><font color="#000000">   (c)</font></b> Is fully authorized to sign the contract and have full capacity to bind itself with the terms of such contract;\n<b><font color="#000000">    (d)</font></b>Is not found to be of unsound mind by a court of competent jurisdiction;\n<b><font color="#000000">    (e)</font></b>Is never been convicted by any court of any offence involving moral turpitude and sentenced in respect thereof to imprisonment for any term.\n<b><font color="#000000">   (f)</font></b>Use its best endeavors to promote, develop and extend sales of the said products throughout the said territory to all potential purchasers thereof and work diligently to obtain orders thereof and work diligently to obtain orders therefore; by means of personal visits to and by correspondence with like as directed by SOLITECK in that behalf, to familiarize purchasers and potential purchasers of the optimum use of and benefit accruing or arising from the said products and/or as may be mutually agreed upon between the parties hereto in writing from time to time.\n<b><font color="#000000">   (g)</font></b> Will carry the business under this contract maintaining proper ethical standards.\n<b><font color="#000000">   (h)</font></b> Not make or give any representations, warranties or guarantees with reference to the said products except as approved of in writing by SOLITECK from time to time and SOLITECK reserves the right to change the terms and conditions of sale time to time.\n<b><font color="#000000">   (i)</font></b> Not incur any liabilities or obligations on behalf of SOLITECK or in any way pledge SoliTeck’s credit or accept any order or make any contract binding upon SOLITECK without its prior consent in writing in that behalf:\n<b><font color="#000000">    (j)</font></b> Not offer the said products for sale at any price lower than the prices fixed from time to time by SOLITECK.\n<b><font color="#000000">    (k)</font></b> Not use SoliTeck’s name and logo for any promotional/ advertising/ marketing etc. without prior written consent from SOLITECK.\n<b><font color="#000000">    (l)</font></b> Promptly bring to the notice of RIPL any information received by the CHANNEL PARTNER which is likely to be of use or benefit to SOLITECK in relation to the marketing, sale and distribution of the said products.\n<b><font color="#000000">    (m)</font></b> Adhere to all directions and instructions given to the CHANNEL PARTNER by SOLITECK in relation to the marketing, sale and distribution of the said products from time to time and, in the absence of any such directions or instructions in relation to any particular matter, shall act in such manner as would be in the best interest of SOLITECK.\n<b><font color="#000000">   (n)</font></b> Obtain, maintain and keep valid &amp; in full force all permit licenses, permissions and the like and comply in all respects with all applicable laws, rules and the regulation and from time to time applicable or relevant to the business, activities and operations herein contemplated.\n<b><font color="#000000">    (o)</font></b> Be required to submit the requisite data for reconciliation purpose as and when required by SOLITECK.\n<b><font color="#000000">   (p)</font></b> Accept the payments from the customers as per applicable laws of India law.\n<b><font color="#000000">    (q)</font></b> Be required to undergo training as provide by SOLITECK on any updations or new ventures.\n<b><font color="#000000">   (r)</font></b> Ensure that at no point of time, any employee/representative of the CHANNEL PARTNER shall claim employment or employment related benefits from SOLITECK.\n<b><font color="#000000">    (s)</font></b> Confirms that SOLITECK provide customer support and fulfillment to its users in accordance with our then-current standard terms and generally to direct users of SOLITECK. CHANNEL PARTNER understand that SOLITECK reserves the right to refuse to provide customer/fulfillment services to any user for a variety of reasons, including but not limited to:</string>
    <string name="aggrement20"><b><font color="#000000">    (t)</font></b> Confirms that services provided by SOLITECK to him will be as reasonable as provided to its customer.
\n<b><font color="#000000">    (u) </font></b> Shall bear all costs relating to trainings, including travel, accommodation and subsistence cost of trainee representatives, though, the training will be free of cost at a venue/ training centre chosen by the SOLITECK at its discretion.</string>
    <string name="aggrement21"><b><font color="#000000">3. TITLE </font></b> The title to the paragraphs/ clauses are given for convenience only and do not have any legal implications/ complications.\n<b><font color="#000000">4. PRICES </font></b> The title to the paragraphs/ clauses are given for convenience only and do not have any legal implications/ complications.</string>
    <string name="aggrement23"><b><font color="#000000">(a)</font></b> The CHANNEL PARTNER shall make payment for the prepaid products in advance to SOLITECK through Bank Transfer/ Demand Draft. No cash payment or direct deposit in bank will be accepted in this regard.
\n<b><font color="#000000">(b)</font></b> Any false statement by the CHANNEL PARTNER related to products/services will be treated as breach of contract and accordingly action will be taken.
\n<b><font color="#000000">(c)</font></b> SOLITECK will not be a party to any dispute of any nature what-so-ever between CHANNEL PARTNER to other Retailer, dealer, sub-dealer or retailer.</string>

    <string name="aggrement27"><b><font color="#000000">(i)</font></b> SOLITECK shall have no liability or obligation for any state or local income tax liability or any other statutory levels &amp; duties etc. of the CHANNEL PARTNER or any person assigned by the CHANNEL PARTNER.
\n<b><font color="#000000">(ii)</font></b> However, nothing contained herein shall prevent SOLITECK from deducting tax at source as required by law and regulation from payment to the CHANNEL PARTNER.</string>
    <string name="aggrement29"><b><font color="#000000">(a)</font></b> SOLITECK reserves the right to add/modify/delete Prepaid/ Postpaid/ DMT/ AEPS/ BBPS products and services as per the current market requirement.
\n<b><font color="#000000">(b)</font></b> In relation to software supplied by SOLITECK to the CHANNEL PARTNER, the CHANNEL PARTNER acknowledges that all intellectual property rights in such software are and shall remain the property of SOLITECK or a third party licenser as the case may be.
</string>
    <string name="aggrement31">The CHANNEL PARTNER will keep a rolling deposit with SOLITECK for providing connectivity to its website for sale of product’s. to its customers. The price against such services will be deducted from rolling deposit. The amount in this rolling deposit will have to be replenished from time to time to use the services provided by SOLITECK.</string>


    <string name="aggrement35"><b><font color="#000000">(a)</font></b> Nothing in this Agreement grants any license or right, beyond that required for the Specified Purpose, under any patent, copyright, trade secret or other Intellectual Property.
\n<b><font color="#000000">(b)</font></b>Neither party will remove any proprietary, copyright, trade secret, confidentiality or other notice from any of the other’s Confidential Information.
\n<b><font color="#000000">(c)</font></b>SOLITECK shall always be the sole and exclusive owner of all the right, title and interest in respect of the intellectual Property Rights of SOLITECK arising out of this agreement. “Intellectual Property Rights” mean all rights, benefits, title or interest in or to any Intellectual Property, anywhere in the world (whether registered or not and including all applications for the same) directly or indirectly under/pursuant to this Agreement.</string>
         <string name="aggrement37"><b><font color="#000000">(a)</font></b> The commission favorable by SOLITECK shall be all inclusive and shall be deemed to include any amounts for Service tax or any other tax as might be payable by SOLITECK to the CHANNEL PARTNER. SOLITECK has the right to change commission structure at its sole option on prospective basis.
\n<b><font color="#000000">(b)</font></b> SOLITECK shall deduct tax and GST or any other deductions at such rates as may be applicable and necessary as pet the prevailing law.</string>-->
   <string name="aggrement39">The CHANNEL PARTNER shall be the del-credere CHANNEL PARTNER of SOLITECK and the shall only be entitled to commission as provided in this Agreement. If as a condition prior thereto, SOLITECK shall have received from the CHANNEL PARTNER the full price of the sale of the said products and shall indemnify SOLITECK from and against all loss caused by the breach or non observance on the part of any purchaser or any contract entered into between the purchaser and SOLITECK.</string>-->
  <string name="aggrement43">Notwithstanding anything herein contained, either party shall have the right to terminate this Agreement forthwith upon the happening of all or any of the following events, namely:\n<b><font color="#000000">(a)</font></b> upon the other making any arrangement or composition with the general body of its creditors or having a winding-up order passed against it or any going into liquidation, voluntary or otherwise than for the purpose of reconstruction or amalgamation;
\n<b><font color="#000000"> (b)</font></b> upon any breach or default by the other of or in any of the terms, conditions or stipulations herein contained and it s failure for a period of not less than thirty days to remedy the same after the receipt by it or written notice from the other in that behalf requiring it so to do.</string>-->
   <string name="aggrement44"><b><font color="#000000">(a)</font></b>On the expiry or earlier termination of this Agreement, the CHANNEL PARTNER shall forthwith return, deliver to SOLITECK all documents, correspondence books of accounts and records, literature, brochures, advertising literature and material, articles and affects, in its possession, custody or control relating or pertaining in any manner to this Agreement without making any copies thereof or extracts there from.
\n<b><font color="#000000">(b)</font></b> On the expiry or sooner determination or purported determination fro any cause whatsoever of this Agreement, the CHANNEL PARTNER:</string>-->
    <string name="aggrement46"><b><font color="#000000"> 1.</font></b> Shall not, directly or indirectly, act or hold itself out in the manner whatsoever as the CHANNEL PARTNER, Retailer or other representative of SOLITECK.
\n<b><font color="#000000"> 2.</font></b> Shall not deal as CHANNEL PARTNER of SOLITECK.
\n<b><font color="#000000"> 3.</font></b> shall promptly return to SOLITECK or otherwise dispose of as SOLITECK directs ant stationary, books, register, promotion, advertising and other materials all other articles and effects whatsoever which are in possession, custody or control of SOLITECK and shall settle all accounts within 6 weeks from the date of termination.
\n<b><font color="#000000"> 4.</font></b> shall not directly or indirectly, use the name , business name, corporate name, trade name, trading style, trade marks, logos, devices, lettering, layout, color scheme or get up in any language, script, form, or representation, visual or oral otherwise which are or is in any way identical or similar to the said trade marks and / or any of them and /or which may in any way adversely effect or dilute the sole and exclusive right, title or interest of SOLITECK in that behalf.</string>-->


<!--    <string name="aggrement7">expression shall, unless it be</string>-->
<!--    <string name="aggrement7">expression shall, unless it be</string>-->



</resources>